<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Assignment3_33906211</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome_screen">Welcome_Screen</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text">
        This app provides general health and nutrition information for educational purposes only.
        It is not intended as medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always consult a qualified
        professional before making any changes to your diet, exercise, or health regimen.\n\n
        Use this app at your own risk. If you would like to see an Accredited Practicing Dietitian (APD),
        please visit the Monash Nutrition Clinic:
    </string>
    <string name="persona_background">
        People can be broadly classified into 6 different types based on their eating preferences.
        Click on ach button below to find out the different types, and select the type that best fits you!
    </string>
    <string name="food_score_description">
        Your Food Quality Score provides a snapshot of how well your eating-patterns align
        with established food guidelines, helping you identify both strengths and
        opportunities for improvement in your diet. \n\n
        This personalized measurement considers various food groups including vegetable,
        fruits, whole grains, and proteins to give you practical insights for making
        healthier food choices.
    </string>
    <string name="GenAi_Prompt">
        Generate a short unique encouraging health tip to improve their healths:
        - References one random specific metric
        - Suggests adding one food from: Fruit, Vegetables, Grains, Red Meat, Seafood, Poultry, Fish, Egg, Nuts/Seeds
        - Uses unique phrasing each time
    </string>
    <string name="GenAi_Pattern_Prompt">
        Please analyse and find one short unique pattern
        - References one random specific metric from: Sex, discretionary, vegetables, fruit,
        grains, whole, meat, dairy, sodium, alcohol, water, sugar, saturated fat, unsaturated fat
        - Uses unique phrasing each time
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_questionnaires_screen">QuestionnairesScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_activity_insight_screen">InsightScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_clinician_screen">ClinicianScreen</string>
</resources>